

## **ABOUT ME**

I'm Diogo, a 25 years old Web developer, from Portugal.

I started learning programming when I was 16 years old, when I took my first course in programming and computer systems. During my journey I went through some languages like php, python, C, C# and javascript. But over time during my first job I started to learn more about javascript and typescript and quickly started to love it and I decided that it was the languages I wanted to focus on and specialize. I've been studying front-end development full-time since then, and in my current job I'm focused on those same languages. Always want learn more, do more and be more. I also firmly believe that we should never settle down.

I'm hard working, super curious, passionate, committed, and also a fast learner!



d96goncalves@gmail.com



+351 911759815



in/dgoncalves96

# TECH STACK / SKILLS

HTML5 - CSS3 - JAVASCRIPT - SASS - WEBPACK - REDUX WEB COMPONENTS - STYLED COMPONENTS - FIREBASE MYSQL - REACT JS - ANGULAR - REDIS - JAVA - NODE JS OPENSHIFT - JENKINS

#### **EDUCATION**

2016 - 2019

Degree in Computer Engineering

 ${\sf ISTEC, Higher\,Institute\,of\,Advanced\,Technologies, Portugal}$ 

EQF Level 6:

2015 - 2016

CTeSP - Networks and computer systems

ISTEC, Higher Institute of Advanced Technologies, Portugal

EOF Level 5:

2013 - 2015

Management and Programming Technican of Informatic Systems

Rainha Dona Leonor, Portugal

EOF Level 4:

## **EXPERIENCE**

# 2019 - The moment Critical Techworks

Lisbon, Portugal

- BMW Car booking application
- Webcomponents for integration of various financing environments

2017 - 2019

Milenar Influence Media

Lisbon, Portugal

- Building web platforms using technologies: PHP, Laravel, MySql, Vue JS, JavaScript, Ruby.

2014 - 2015

Nova University - Computer Science Research Technial Helpdesk

Lisbon Portugal

- Training in Work Context (internship) whitin the professional course of Technician of Management and Programming of Computer Systems.

HOOBIES / PASSIONS











